<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Adam Brocklehurst</title>
    <link>https://avbrocklehurst.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Adam Brocklehurst</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 15:23:31 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://avbrocklehurst.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Making ASCII GIFs</title>
      <link>https://avbrocklehurst.github.io/posts/making-ascii-gifs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 15:23:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://avbrocklehurst.github.io/posts/making-ascii-gifs/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to a combination of a little snow in the UK, a cancelled flight, and a lot of rain in Lisbon, I recently ended up spending a day stuck in a hotel room. So I did what any bored software engineer does, mess about and write some code.
A couple of days earlier at work, we updated our Github slack integration. Github has released an updated version for non-enterprise users that was much prettier and gave a lot of nice functionality from slack commands rather than having to go to an admin page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me</title>
      <link>https://avbrocklehurst.github.io/posts/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://avbrocklehurst.github.io/posts/me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I’m Adam.
I’m a software engineer who really loves blogs. I, however, really suck at writing. In university I once managed to get 19% on an essay.
I’d love to be able to write well-articulated blog posts that can excite readers about topics I am passionate about, and the only way I am going to get better at that is by doing it.
So this blog is for me to get better at writing technical (and some non-technical) blog posts, and hopefully at some point along the way they will become readable and enjoyable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>